A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1940-1946 FA758
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1946
  - Czechoslovakia, 1946; 1946/712
    - Czechoslovakia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1946; 1946/712.E
      - Czechoslovakia, 1946 (Box 349, Folder 2367)
    - Czechoslovakia - Public Health Education, 1946; 1946/712.L
      - Czechoslovakia, 1946 (Box 349, Folder 2367)
  - Denmark, 1946; 1946/713
    - Denmark, 1946 (Box 350, Folder 2368)
    - Denmark - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1946; 1946/713.E
      - Denmark, 1946 (Box 350, Folder 2368)
    - Denmark - Humanities and Arts, 1946; 1946/713.R
      - Denmark, 1946 (Box 350, Folder 2368)
  - Estonia, 1946; 1946/714
    - Estonia, 1946 (Box 350, Folder 2368)
  - Scandinavia, 1946; 1946/716
    - Scandinavia, 1946 (Box 350, Folder 2368)
  - Germany, 1946; 1946/717
    - Germany - (A-Z), 1946 (Box 350, Folder 2369)
    - Germany - Publications, 1946 (Box 350, Folder 2370)
    - Germany - Medical Sciences, 1946; 1946/717.A
      - Germany, 1946 (Box 350, Folder 2370)
    - Germany - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1946; 1946/717.D
      - Germany, 1946 (Box 350, Folder 2370)
    - Germany - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1946; 1946/717.E
      - Germany, 1946 (Box 350, Folder 2370)
    - Germany - Humanities and Arts, 1946; 1946/717.R
      - Germany, 1946 (Box 350, Folder 2370)
    - Germany - Social Sciences, 1946; 1946/717.S
      - Germany, 1946 (Box 350, Folder 2370)
  - Tanganyika, 1946; 1946/723
    Tanzania
    - Tanganyika, 1946 (Box 350, Folder 2370)
  - Greece, 1946; 1946/749
    - Greece, 1946 (Box 350, Folder 2370)
    - Greece - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1946; 1946/749.D
      - Greece, 1946 (Box 350, Folder 2370)
  - Hungary, 1946; 1946/750
    - Hungary - (A-K), 1946 (Box 350, Folder 2371)
    - Hungary - (L-Z), 1946 (Box 350, Folder 2372)
    - Hungary - Medical Sciences, 1946; 1946/750.A
      - Hungary, 1946 (Box 350, Folder 2372)
    - Hungary - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1946; 1946/750.D
      - Hungary, 1946 (Box 350, Folder 2372)
    - Hungary - Humanities and Arts, 1946; 1946/750.R
      - Hungary, 1946 (Box 350, Folder 2372)
  - Italy, 1946; 1946/751
    - Italy, 1946 (Box 350, Folder 2373)
    - Italy - Medical Sciences, 1946; 1946/751.A
      - Italy, 1946 (Box 350, Folder 2373)
    - Italy - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1946; 1946/751.E
      - Italy, 1946 (Box 350, Folder 2373)
    - Italy - Humanities and Arts, 1946; 1946/751.R
      - Italy, 1946 (Box 350, Folder 2373)
  - Liberia, 1946; 1946/759
    - Liberia, 1946 (Box 351, Folder 2374)
  - Luxembourg, 1946; 1946/760
    Luxembourg
    - Luxembourg, 1946 (Box 351, Folder 2374)
  - Norway, 1946; 1946/767
    - Norway, 1946 (Box 351, Folder 2374)
    - Norway - Medical Sciences, 1946; 1946/767.A
      - Norway, 1946 (Box 351, Folder 2374)
    - Norway - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1946; 1946/767.D
      - Norway, 1946 (Box 351, Folder 2374)
    - Norway - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1946; 1946/767.E
      - Norway, 1946 (Box 351, Folder 2374)
    - Norway - Humanities and Arts, 1946; 1946/767.R
      - Norway, 1946 (Box 351, Folder 2374)
  - Iran, 1946; 1946/771
    - Iran, 1946 (Box 351, Folder 2375)
  - Portugal, 1946; 1946/773
    - Portugal, 1946 (Box 351, Folder 2375)
  - Romania, 1946; 1946/783
    - Romania, 1946 (Box 351, Folder 2375)
  - Ukraine, 1946; 1946/784
    - Ukraine - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1946; 1946/784.E
      - Ukraine, 1946 (Box 351, Folder 2375)
  - U.S.S.R., 1946; 1946/785
    - USSR, 1946 (Box 351, Folder 2376)
    - U.S.S.R. - Medical Sciences, 1946; 1946/785.A
      - USSR, 1946 (Box 351, Folder 2376)
    - U.S.S.R. - Humanities and Arts, 1946; 1946/785.R
      - USSR, 1946 (Box 351, Folder 2376)
    - U.S.S.R. - Social Sciences, 1946; 1946/785.S
      - USSR, 1946 (Box 351, Folder 2376)
  - Latvia, 1946; 1946/786
    Latvia
    - Latvia, 1946 (Box 351, Folder 2377)
  - Finland, 1946; 1946/787
    - Finland, 1946 (Box 351, Folder 2377)
    - Finland - Medical Sciences, 1946; 1946/787.A
      - Finland, 1946 (Box 351, Folder 2377)
    - Finland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1946; 1946/787.E
      - Finland, 1946 (Box 351, Folder 2377)
    - Finland - Humanities and Arts, 1946; 1946/787.R
      - Finland, 1946 (Box 351, Folder 2377)
    - Finland - Social Sciences, 1946; 1946/787.S
      - Finland, 1946 (Box 351, Folder 2377)
  - Lithuania, 1946; 1946/788
    - Lithnania, 1946 (Box 351, Folder 2377)
  - Poland, 1946; 1946/789
    - Poland, 1946 (Box 351, Folder 2378)
    - Poland - Medical Sciences, 1946; 1946/789.A
      - Poland, 1946 (Box 351, Folder 2378)
    - Poland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1946; 1946/789.E
      - Poland, 1946 (Box 351, Folder 2378)
    - Poland - Health Services, 1946; 1946/789.K
      - Poland, 1946 (Box 351, Folder 2378)
    - Poland - Public Health Education, 1946; 1946/789.L
      - Poland, 1946 (Box 351, Folder 2378)
    - Poland - Social Sciences, 1946; 1946/789.S
      - Poland, 1946 (Box 351, Folder 2378)
  - Sweden, 1946; 1946/800
    - Sweden, 1946 (Box 351, Folder 2379)
    - Sweden - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1946; 1946/800.E
      - Sweden, 1946 (Box 351, Folder 2379)
    - Sweden - Social Sciences, 1946; 1946/800.S
      - Sweden, 1946 (Box 351, Folder 2379)
  - Switzerland, 1946; 1946/803
    - Switzerland, 1946 (Box 352, Folder 2380)
    - Switzerland - Medical Sciences, 1946; 1946/803.A
      - Switzerland, 1946 (Box 352, Folder 2380)
    - Switzerland - Humanities and Arts, 1946; 1946/803.R
      - Switzerland, 1946 (Box 352, Folder 2380)
  - Near East Region, 1946; 1946/804
    - Near East Region - Humanities and Arts, 1946; 1946/804.R
      - Near East Region, 1946 (Box 352, Folder 2381)
  - Turkey, 1946; 1946/805
    - Turkey, 1946 (Box 352, Folder 2382)
    - Turkey - Medical Sciences, 1946; 1946/805.A
      - Turkey, 1946 (Box 352, Folder 2382)
    - Turkey - Declinations, 1946; 1946/805.F
      - Turkey, 1946 (Box 352, Folder 2382)
  - Saudi Arabia and Oman, 1946; 1946/817
    Saudi Arabia
    - Saudi Arabia, 1946 (Box 352, Folder 2382)
  - Israel, 1946; 1946/825
    Israel
    - Israel, 1946 (Box 352, Folder 2382)
    - Israel - Declinations, 1946; 1946/825.F
      - Israel, 1946 (Box 352, Folder 2382)
  - Lebanon, 1946; 1946/833
    - Lebanon, 1946 (Box 352, Folder 2382)
    - Lebanon - Nursing, 1946; 1946/833.C
      - Lebanon, 1946 (Box 352, Folder 2382)